PAUL CERVANTES

Hawthorne, CA 90250 | 3102273250 | paulcervantes2244@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic individual experienced in analyzing issues on service calls and finding effective solutions. Offering engaging and pleasant personality with expertise building customer relationships. Outstanding diagnostics skills. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Detail-oriented team player with strong organizational skills. Ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously with a high degree of accuracy.

Skills

- Remote Support Management
- Blueprint Reading
- System Maintenance
- Schematics Interpretation
- Testing and Repair
- Instrument Calibration
- Quality Control

- Attention to Detail
- Operating Systems: Windows, Mac, Linux
- System Installation
- Customer Service
- System Troubleshooting
- Maintenance and Repairs

Work History

Lead Technician 08/2021 to Current

Drink Command - Los Angeles, CA

- Mentored junior technicians in maintenance, repair and reporting duties.
- Performed troubleshooting and diagnosis on malfunctioning equipment.
- Repaired, upgraded and inspected electronic, electrical and mechanical systems.
- Tracked equipment and inventory, maintaining prescribed levels for technical equipment and supplies.
- Fostered relationships with internal and external customers.
- Tested components and systems to evaluate performance and identify concerns.
- Implemented, configured, and optimized safety standards.

Inventory Associate

02/2019 to 04/2022

King Keg - Hawthorne, CA

- Completed physical inventory counts each month.
- Managed inventory storage in clean and organized fashion.

- Used hand-held devices and computers to record and monitor inventory levels and completed audits to uncover and address inaccuracies.
- Maintained inventory count, tracked usage, and documented variances.
- Performed data entry and completed proper paperwork.
- Monitored and adjusted inventory levels to meet customer needs and demands.
- Verified orders by comparing names and quantity of items packaged with shipping documents.
- Worked effectively with shippers to resolve shipment issues, damaged materials and shortages.

Fiber Laser Operator 06/2019 to 05/2021

Arrow Metal Stamping - Hawthorne, CA

- Moved steel plates, laser cut items and scrap metal using safe lifting practices.
- Loaded, installed and set up tools required for laser operation.
- Uploaded proper program from machine control and established optimal laser cutting conditions.
- Met time and quality expectations by completing accurate work in line with specifications.
- Understood and executed orders given by laser programmer and senior production staff.
- Moved finished work to correct staging area for disposition.
- Instructed new employees on operation of CNC machines.

Education

Native or Bilingual

	.
English	Spanish
Languages	
North Torrance - Torrance, CA	
High School Diploma	06/2017
Education	

Professional Working